# Code with Jalga

**Email:** jjcoding2020@gmail.com **Mobile:** +996 778 163 749

Website: link to project

I know I don't have much experience, which might make you decline my CV, that's why I'm ready to work for

FREE till you say I started bringing value to your company.

I just want you to know how passionate I'm about tech and web development.

Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, React.js, Axios, Tailwind, Bootstrap.

**Some knowledge of:** Python, Django, DRF, Selenium, Pandas, Flask, Postgres, MongoDB, Express.js with Node.js.

#### Education

UdemyOnlineThe Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp2023

UdemyOnlineThe Complete Python Pro Bootcamp for 20232022-2023

Girne American University

International Business Management (Master's Degree)

Cyprus
2018-2020

Tomsk State University of Architecture and BuildingRussiaExpertise and Real Estate Management (Bachelor's Degree)2014-2018

# **Experience**

## **Durmaz Techno Store**

Sales Manager

Cyprus, Famagusta Sept. 2020 – May 2022

- Brought to the department a structure which increased sales.
- Gained a huge amount of new customers, the company opened another branch due to increasing demand.

#### 2SUNS Real Estate Agency

Marketing Manager

Cyprus, Famagusta July 2019 – Sept. 2020

- Participated in International Exhibitions to present real estate of Cyprus, and gained new customers
- Main impact I did here was improving ads of the company, the quality of content.

# **Projects**

Frontend project

Kyrgyz Republic, Bishkek Oct. 2023

## Portfolio website

Repository link to project

- Built this web-app to showcase my portfolio projects.
- Technologies I used Django, DRF, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Postgresql, Authentication etc.

Users are able to:

- View the optimal layout depending on their device's screen size
- See hover states for interactive elements
- See my portfolio projects
- Visit a repository of any project shown on the page
- Download my CV in pdf format
- Send me an email
- Get links to my social media accounts for connections

Full-stack project

Kyrgyz Republic, Bishkek Sept. 2023

#### To-do-list

Repository link to project

- Built this web-app keep track of things I do.
- Technologies I used Django, DRF, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Postgresql, Authentication etc.

Users are able to:

- View the optimal layout depending on their device's screen size
- See hover states for interactive elements
- See a list of all tasks
- See a number of incomplete tasks
- Add a task
- Update a task
- Delete a task
- Register
- Login
- Update Profile
- Update Password
- Delete Profile

Check my website to see more of my projects.